Guide to the Paula Kamen Papers, 1970-2006 and undated (bulk 1991-2002) RL.00765
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Writings Series, 1982-2005 and undated, 50 boxes
  - Seven Dates with Seven Writers, 1996-2002, 2 boxes
    Seven Dates with Seven Writers is billed as an unromantic comedy. This subseries is comprised primarily of drafts and also includes correspondence and materials related to productions of the play. Files are arranged alphabetically.
    - Correspondence, 1998-2002, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1996 July 8 (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1996 July 9 (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1996 September 5 (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1997 January 5 (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1997 December 5 (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1997 December 6 (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1998 February 5, 2 folders (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1998 April 29 (Box 42)
    - Draft, 1998 June 17 (Box 42)
    - Drafts, undated (Box 43)
    - Chicago Dramatist production, 1998 August (Box 43)
    - Improv Olympic production, 1998 October (Box 43)
    - Promotional poster (Box 43, Oversize-folder 138, Folder 1)
    - Promotional poster (Box 43, Oversize-folder OC:IV:13, Folder 2)
  - Other Writings, 1982-2005 and undated, 8 boxes
    Comprised of drafts and research completed by Kamen for shorter pieces she has authored or planned, such as articles (including those written while a college student, for the Daily Illini) and chapters of books. Files are arranged alphabetically by project name.
    - Anthology, 2002 (Box 43)
    - Aquaintance rape article, Folders 1-4 of 6 (Box 43)
    - Aquaintance rape article, Folders 5-6 of 6 (Box 44)
    - Chicago Women's Liberation Union (Box 44)
    - Clippings, 2 folders (Box 44)
    - Column proposal, 1991 (Box 44)
    - A Cure For AIDS, 1995 July (Box 44)
    - Daily Illini, 1982-1987 (Box 45)
    - Daily Illini, 1988-1989 (Box 45)
    - Females and sports research (Box 45)
    - Feminists have better sex lives (Box 45)
    - Freelance, 1995 (Box 45)
    - Girls anthology, Folders 1-2 of 5 (Box 45)
    - Girls anthology, Folders 3-5 of 5 (Box 46)
    - Girls and cruelty review, 2003, 3 folders (Box 46)
    - Go Fish Film Review, 2 folders (Box 46)
    - Higher education and gender gap article, 5 folders (Box 47)
    - Homo-Neurotic, 1995 May, 2 folders (Box 47)
    - How to Get Yourself Heard, 1998 (Box 48)
    - Kenosha, 1990 (Box 48)
    - Men stopping rape, 1990 (Box 48)
    - Next Anthology, 1995 (Box 48)
    - Notes on music (Box 48)
    - Other articles (Box 48)
    - Other writings (Box 48)
    - Our Bodies, Ourselves (Box 48)
    - Ruminator, 2004 (Box 48)
    - Ruminator, 2005 (Box 48)
    - Sex attitudes book proposal (Box 49)
    - Carol Siegel, 2002 (Box 49)
    - Soap opera article (Box 49)
    - Speak Out booklet (Box 49)
    - Sugar shack, 1993 (Box 49)
    - Why I Can No Longer Afford to be Leftist, 1996 (Box 49)
    - Women's bodies, 1994, 2 folders (Box 49)
    - Women's Project Productions (Box 49)
    - Clippings notebook, 1986-1989 (Box 94)
  - Other Files, 1993-1999, 2 boxes
    Comprised of materials relating to Kamen's writing career but not to specific projects. Files include primarily correspondence, and also present are notebooks and publicity-related material.
    - Correspondence (Box 50)
    - Funding for women and girls (Box 50)
    - Laura Gross correspondence, 1993-1995 (Box 50)
    - Hollywood writing correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 50)
    - Kamen cited (Box 50)
    - Notebooks, 4 folders (Box 50)
    - Notebooks (Box 51)
    - Publicity-related, 1993-1995, 2 folders (Box 51)
    - Publishing (Box 51)
    - Quotes (Box 51)
- Conferences and Engagements Series, 1991-2006, 3 boxes
  Materials in this series document Kamen's frequent speaking engagements at college and university campuses, bookstores, and conferences throughout the 1990s. A significant number of these talks were in support of her books Feminist Fatale and Her Way. Often the same talk was used for a number of events and adjusted accordingly. Folders are arranged alphabetically by folder title, which is frequently the location name of an event.
  - Bowling Green State University, 1996 (Box 52)
  - Clark University, 1999 February 7 (Box 52)
  - College of St. Catherine, 1996 November 13 (Box 52)
  - College public relations, 3 folders (Box 52)
  - Lecture notes, 2002, 2 folders (Box 52)
  - Neal Pollack event, 2001 January (Box 52)
  - Profiles (Box 52)
  - Publicity, 1991-1994 (Box 53)
  - Scripts and produced plays (Box 53)
  - Sex book talk, 1997 May 22 (Box 53)
  - Speaking, 1996 (Box 53)
  - Speaking, 1997, 2 folders (Box 53)
  - Speaking, 1998-1999 (Box 53)
  - Speaking, 1999-2001 (Box 53)
  - Speaking: letters (Box 53)
  - Speeches: memorabilia, 2006 (Box 53)
  - Theater, 1992-1995 (Box 53)
  - Theater, 1996 (Box 53)
  - Theater/television, 1998-1999 (Box 54)
  - Theater: media (Box 54)
  - Truckee Meadows Community College, 1997 March 7 (Box 54)
  - Union College, 1996 February 13 (Box 54)
  - University of Chicago, 1996 May 3 (Box 54)
  - Valdosta State University, 1999 March 5 (Box 54)
  - Winona State University, 2000 March 3 (Box 54)
  - Women's Studies conferences, 2 folders (Box 54)
  - Promotional posters (2 items) (Box 54, Oversize-folder OC:IV:13, Folder 2)
- Subject Files Series, 1970-2002, 26 boxes
  Kamen maintained extensive files on a wide range of subjects pertaining to her writing interests. Topics covered include feminism, activism, politics, popular culture, and sex, along with many others. These files consist primarily of clippings from magazines, newspapers, and other publications. Folders are arranged alphabetically by subject.
  - Activism: feminist organizing, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Activism: National Organization for Women (NOW) (Box 55)
  - Activism: students, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - Advertisements (Box 55)
  - Affirmative action (Box 55)
  - AIDS, 2 folders (Box 55)
  - AIDS, 1996 (Box 55)
  - AIDS and safe sex, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Art (Box 56)
  - Anal [sex] (Box 56)
  - Babybusters (Box 56)
  - Backlash (Box 56)
  - Beauty, 2 folders (Box 56)
  - Birth control, 3 folders (Box 56)
  - Birth rates, 1999 (Box 57)
  - Bisexuals (Box 57)
  - Black women (Box 57)
  - Bobbit, Lorena (Box 57)
  - Books (Box 57)
  - Book reviews (Box 57)
  - Braun, Carol Mosley (Box 57)
  - Breast cancer (Box 57)
  - Breast feeding (Box 57)
  - Breast implants (Box 57)
  - Campus feminists/women's centers (Box 57)
  - Campus rape (Box 57)
  - Campus safe sex (Box 57)
  - Careers (Box 57)
  - Careers, 3 folders (Box 58)
  - Careers: nontraditional (Box 58)
  - Celebrities, 2 folders (Box 58)
  - Childcare (Box 58)
  - Child support (Box 58)
  - Choice/abortion (Box 58)
  - Civil rights (Box 58)
  - Clinton, Hilary (Box 58)
  - Cohabitation (Box 58)
  - Colleges (Box 58)
  - Colleges: behavior (Box 58)
  - Colleges: East coast 1990 November (Box 59)
  - Colleges: newspapers (Box 59)
  - Communication and consent (Box 59)
  - Confidence and self-esteem (Box 59)
  - Confusion (Box 59)
  - Corporations (Box 59)
  - Corporations: non-profit (Box 59)
  - Culture (Box 59)
  - Chicago Women's AIDS Project (CWAP) (Box 59)
  - Dating (Box 59)
  - Demographics (Box 59)
  - Displaced homemakers (Box 59)
  - Discrimination (Box 59)
  - Diversity (Box 59)
  - Diversity (Box 60)
  - Divorce (Box 60)
  - Domestic violence, 3 folders (Box 60)
  - Domestic violence: pre-1994 (Box 60)
  - Domestic violence: O.J. Simpson news (Box 60)
  - Domestic violence: O.J. Simpson and media (Box 60)
  - Eating disorders (Box 60)
  - Education, 2 folders (Box 60)
  - Education: Citadel (Box 60)
  - Elderly (Box 60)
  - Elders, Jocelyn (Box 60)
  - Environment (Box 60)
  - Erotica (Box 60)
  - Experts (Box 60)
  - Fairness and Accuracy in Reporting (FAIR) (Box 60)
  - Family, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Family: stabilizing (Box 61)
  - Fantasy (Box 61)
  - Feminists and sex lives (Box 61)
  - Fetal issues (Box 61)
  - Film, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Fraternities (Box 61)
  - Free speech on campus (Box 61)
  - Funding, 2 folders (Box 61)
  - Gay: openness (Box 61)
  - Gay: teens (Box 61)
  - Gays and media, 2 folders (Box 62)
  - Gays and military (Box 62)
  - Gender (Box 62)
  - Generation Y (Box 62)
  - Girls (Box 62)
  - Grunge (Box 62)
  - Harrassment, 3 folders (Box 62)
  - Harrassment, 1996 (Box 62)
  - Health/black women's health (Box 63)
  - Hill, Anita (Box 63)
  - Hollywood (Box 63)
  - Hollywood, 2002 (Box 63)
  - Housing (Box 63)
  - Infant mortality (Box 63)
  - Intermarriage (Box 63)
  - International (Box 63)
  - Jews (Box 63)
  - Jones, Paula (Box 63)
  - Language (Box 63)
  - Law (Box 63)
  - Lesbian and gay: sadism/masochism (S/M) (Box 63)
  - Lesbian and gay: students, Washington D.C. (Box 63)
  - Lesbians, 1993 (Box 64)
  - Lesbians, 1997 (Box 64)
  - Lesbians: general, 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Lesbian rights, 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Lewinsky, Monica, 2 folders (Box 64)
  - Locker room talk (Box 64)
  - Madonna (Box 65)
  - Magazines (Box 65)
  - Magazines: Cosmopolitan (Box 65)
  - Magazines: Essence (Box 65)
  - Magazines: Playboy and men's (Box 65)
  - Magazines: women, 2 folders (Box 65)
  - Marriage (Box 65)
  - Marriage: gays (Box 65)
  - Marriage and labor force (Box 65)
  - Masturbation (Box 65)
  - Media, 2 folders (Box 66)
  - Medicine: women and medicine (Box 66)
  - Men, 3 folders (Box 66)
  - Menstruation and fertility (Box 66)
  - Military (Box 67)
  - Minorities (Box 67)
  - Mobility (Box 67)
  - Monogamy (Box 67)
  - Morality (Box 67)
  - Motherhood (Box 67)
  - Movement: feminism (Box 67)
  - Movement: feminism, 1970s (Box 67)
  - Movement: feminism, 1992 (Box 67)
  - Movement: feminism, 1996-1999 (Box 67)
  - Movement: feminism, pre-1990 (Box 67)
  - MTV (Box 67)
  - Music (Box 68)
  - Music: Amos, Tori (Box 68)
  - Music: blacks (Box 68)
  - Music: country (Box 68)
  - Music: DiFranco, Ani (Box 68)
  - Music: Feminism (Box 68)
  - Music: gay and bisexual (Box 68)
  - Music: Harvey, P.J. (Box 68)
  - Music: L7 (Box 68)
  - Music: Courtney Love (Box 68)
  - Music: Men (Box 68)
  - Music: Morissette, Alanis (Box 68)
  - Music: Phair, Liz (Box 68)
  - Music: politics (Box 68)
  - Music: positive force, 2 folders (Box 68)
  - Music: riot grrrl and punk, 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Music: women in rock, 1999 (Box 69)
  - NOW, 2 folders (Box 69)
  - Openness (Box 69)
  - Openness and controversy (Box 69)
  - Oral sex (Box 69)
  - Orgasm (Box 69)
  - Pay equity (Box 69)
  - Political correctness (PC) (Box 69)
  - Political correctness (PC): college: criticism (Box 69)
  - Peers: equality (Box 69)
  - Politics: women in politics, 2 folders (Box 70)
  - Population (Box 70)
  - Pornography, Folders 1-4 of 8 (Box 70)
  - Pornography, Folders 5-8 of 8 (Box 71)
  - Pornography: future sex (Box 71)
  - Poverty, 2 folders (Box 71)
  - Pregnancy (Box 71)
  - Prisons (Box 71)
  - Prostitutes (Box 71)
  - Progressives (Box 72)
  - Race (Box 72)
  - Radio (Box 72)
  - Rape, 6 folders (Box 72)
  - Rape, 1994-1999 (Box 72)
  - Rape: media (Box 73)
  - Rape: men stopping rape (Box 73)
  - Rape: West coast, 1990 September (Box 73)
  - Rape and sex politics, 2 folders (Box 73)
  - Rape research (Box 73)
  - Reader's Guide to Periodical Literature (Box 73)
  - Religion (Box 73)
  - Religion: Catholic (Box 73)
  - Religion: Catholic: College of St. Catherine (Box 73)
  - Religion: Catholic: women (Box 74)
  - Religion: Christian (Box 74)
  - Religion: gays and religion (Box 74)
  - Religion: HW (Box 74)
  - Religion: Islam (Box 74)
  - Roiphe, Katie, 2 folders (Box 74)
  - Romance (Box 74)
  - Self-defense (Box 74)
  - Self-help (Box 74)
  - Sex abuse (Box 74)
  - Sex: behavior: magazine surveys (Box 75)
  - Sex: freedom/shame (Box 75)
  - Sex: online information (Box 75)
  - Sex: premarital (Box 75)
  - Sex: safe sex: Michigan condom store (Box 75)
  - Sex: safe sex: openness (Box 75)
  - Sex: safe sex: public education (Box 75)
  - Sex assault and media (Box 75)
  - Sex education and information (Box 75)
  - Sex research (Box 75)
  - Sex study: University of Chicago, 2 folders (Box 76)
  - Sex toys (Box 76)
  - Sexism (Box 76)
  - Sexual health (Box 76)
  - Sexual pleasure (Box 76)
  - Sexual revolution (Box 76)
  - Sexuality (Box 76)
  - Sexually aggressive women (Box 76)
  - Shame (Box 76)
  - Single life (Box 76)
  - Single moms (Box 76)
  - Single moms, 1996 (Box 76)
  - Single parents (Box 76)
  - The Sixties (1960s) (Box 77)
  - S/M (sadism and masochism) (Box 77)
  - Smith, William Kennedy (Box 77)
  - South Suburban, Illinois (Box 77)
  - Spirituality (Box 77)
  - Sports (Box 77)
  - State of the media, 1994 (Box 77)
  - Sexually transmitted diseases (STDs) (Box 77)
  - Strippers (Box 77)
  - Statistics, 1996 (Box 77)
  - Sugar Shack (Box 77)
  - Superrats (aggressive women) (Box 77)
  - Tailhook (Box 77)
  - Teenagers (Box 77)
  - Technology (Box 77)
  - Twenty-somethings (Box 77)
  - Television: Kaiser Foundation studies (Box 77)
  - Television, 2 folders (Box 78)
  - Television: MTV (Box 78)
  - Television: soap operas (Box 78)
  - Television: talk shows (Box 78)
  - Television: TV movies (Box 78)
  - Theater (Box 78)
  - Theorists (Box 78)
  - Thomas, Clarence (Box 78)
  - Transgender/transsexual (Box 78)
  - Transvestites/gender benders (Box 78)
  - Tyson, Mike (Box 78)
  - Union/labor (Box 78)
  - Universities and sex correctness (Box 78)
  - Violence (Box 78)
  - Virginia Slims Opinion Poll, 2000 (Box 79)
  - Virginity, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Weddings (Box 79)
  - Women's Information Network (WIN) (Box 79)
  - Women's colleges (Box 79)
  - Women's studies, 2 folders (Box 79)
  - Work and family, Folder 1 of 2 (Box 79)
  - Work and family, Folder 2 of 2 (Box 80)
  - Young feminists, 1997 (Box 80)
  - Young women, 3 folders (Box 80)
  - Youth Jobs (Box 80)
- Audiovisual Materials Series, 1990-2004 and undated, 13 boxes; About 550 items
  Conditions Governing Access note
  [Technical Services may need to have use copies made before items in this series may be accessed. Please consult with Research Services staff before coming to use these materials.]
  This series contains audio cassettes, micro cassettes, compact discs, videotapes, and photographs. A significant majority of these materials are recordings of interviews conducted by Kamen during the course of researching her books and articles. Other recordings are from conferences attended by Kamen, a production of Kamen's play, Seven Dates with Seven Writers, and copies of television programs which included appearances by Kamen. Materials are arranged alphabetically by format, alphabetically within each format, and each recorded item is assigned an alpha-numeric identifier. Use copies will be created upon request; advance notification is highly encouraged. Photographic material consists of photographs taken at the 1993 March on Washington for Lesbian and Gay Rights and at an undated production of Kamen's play, Seven Dates with Seven Writers. A small number of unidentifiable photographs are also included.
  - Audio Cassettes, 1990-2004 and undated, 226 items
    - OR-1 Allison, SMU, 1993 November 20 (1 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-2 Allison, SMU, 1993 November 20 (2 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-3 Amber, 2003 November 11 (Box 81)
    - OR-4 American Headache Society (AHS)(1 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-5 AHS (2 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-6 AHS (3 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-7 AHS, Conceptual Issues Surrounding Headache, 2000 June (4 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-8 AHS, Chronic Daily Headache, 2000 June (5 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-9 AHS, The Neurocognitive Impact of Headache, 2000 June (6 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-10 AHS, The New Headache Consortium, 2000 June (7 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-11 AHS, The New Headache Consortium, 2000 June (8 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-12 AHS, Chronic Daily Headache, 2000 June (9 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-13 AHS, Sustained Opioid Therapy for Intractable Headaches (10 of 10) (Box 81)
    - OR-14 American Pain Society, The Changing Face of Pain, 2003 March (1 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-15 APS, Complementary and Alternative Modalities in Pain Treatment: A Focus on Massage Therapy and Acupuncture Effects and Mechanisms, 2003 March (2 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-16 APS, The Evolution of Pain Theories (3 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-17 APS, Fibromyalgia: Current Understanding and Future Directions, 2003 March (4 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-18 APS, Plenary Session: Invasive Procedures for the Treatment of Pain: Past, Present, and Future, 2003 March (5 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-19 APS, Prediction the Development of Chronic Pain: Data from Prospective Studies, 2003 March (6 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-20 APS, Sex Differences in Pain and Analgesia, 2003 March (7 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-21 APS, Sex, Gender, and Pain, 2003 March (8 of 8) (Box 81)
    - OR-22 Amy, 1993 November 18 (1 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-23 Amy, 1993 November 18 (2 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-24 Anne & Jim, 2003 May 11 (Box 81)
    - OR-25 Arcana, September 21 (Box 81)
    - OR-26 Bakos, Men's Health (Box 81)
    - OR-27 Becky, New York City, 1993 October 7 (Box 81)
    - OR-28 Belly & Mike (Box 81)
    - OR-29 B., Rachel, 2003 November 10 (Box 81)
    - OR-30 B., Heather, 1999 October 25 (1 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-31 B., Heather, 1999 October 25 (2 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-32 B., Paula, 1992 September 1 (1 of 3) (Box 81)
    - OR-33 B., Paula, 1992 September 1 (2 of 3) (Box 81)
    - OR-34 B., Paula, 1992 September 1 (3 of 3) (Box 81)
    - OR-35 Boots (1 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-36 Boots (1 of 2) (Box 81)
    - OR-37 Brooklyn Females, 1993 October 11 (Box 81)
    - OR-38 Carla, January 17 (Box 81)
    - OR-39 Center on Addiction and Substance Abuse (CASA) (1 of 5) (Box 82)
    - OR-40 CASA, Feeling No Pain, Pain & Addiction: Is It All in the Brain?, 2003 February 27 (2 of 5) (Box 82)
    - OR-41 CASA, Feeling No Pain, The Marketing of Pain Relief, 2003 February 27 (3 of 5) (Box 82)
    - OR-42 CASA, Feeling No Pain, More Than A Quick Fix: Are We Treating Pain Adequately?, 2003 February 27 (4 of 5) (Box 82)
    - OR-43 CASA, Feeling No Pain, Diversion: Medical Judgment and the Judgment of Medicine, 2003 February 27 (5 of 5) (Box 82)
    - OR-44 CATALYST: Student Environmental Action Coalition, Champagne, IL, 1999 October (1 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-45 CATALYST: Student Environmental Action Coalition, Champagne, IL, 1999 October (2 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-46 Chicago AIDS (Box 82)
    - OR-47 Chris, 1990 December 10 (1 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-48 Chris, 1990 December 10 (2 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-49 Chronic pain, 2000 January 24 (Box 82)
    - OR-50 Clarke (1 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-51 Clarke (2 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-52 C., Ann, interview (Box 82)
    - OR-53 Crystal, 1992 October 23 (Box 82)
    - OR-54 Kris and Diane, Daryl (1 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-55 Kris and Diane, Daryl (2 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-56 D., Denham (Box 82)
    - OR-57 D., Tamara, 2003 November 5 (Box 82)
    - OR-58 D., Dean November 19 (Box 82)
    - OR-59 Debbie and Rick, Texas (Box 82)
    - OR-60 D., Ivonne, 2003 May 27 (Box 82)
    - OR-61 D., Jack, 2003 May 27 (Box 82)
    - OR-62 D., Schultz, date rape, 1996 (Box 82)
    - OR-63 Dworken (Box 82)
    - OR-64 E., Victoria, 1994 January 25 (1 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-65 E., Victoria, 1994 January 25 (2 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-66 Famay (Box 82)
    - OR-67 F., Julie (1 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-68 F., Julie (2 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-69 Freeman (Box 82)
    - OR-70 F., Daryl (Box 82)
    - OR-71 G., Kathy, 2004 January 14 (Box 82)
    - OR-72 G., Nancy (Box 82)
    - OR-73 Gilbert, 1996 February 7 (1 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-75 Gilbert, 1996 February 7 (2 of 2) (Box 82)
    - OR-76 Go Fish, Michigan, 1994 (Box 83)
    - OR-77 Golden (1 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-78 Golden (2 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-79 G., Marie (Box 83)
    - OR-80 H., Denise, 2004 January 17 (1 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-81 H., Denise, 2004 January 17 (2 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-82 Hampshire panel (Box 83)
    - OR-83 Hanlon, 1993 October 10 (1 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-84 Hanlon, 1993 October 10 (2 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-85 H., Iris and Dave (Box 83)
    - OR-86 H., Elizabeth, 2003 May 15 (Box 83)
    - OR-87 H., Jody P. (1 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-88 H., Jody P.(2 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-89 Haydrel (1 of 3) (Box 83)
    - OR-90 Haydrel (2 of 3) (Box 83)
    - OR-91 Haydrel (3 of 3) (Box 83)
    - OR-92 Headache meeting, National Headache Foundation, 2003 April 23 (Box 83)
    - OR-93 Headache show, NPR, Terry Gross, 2001 April 5 (Box 83)
    - OR-94 H., Rebecca L., 1993 July 30 (1 of 3) (Box 83)
    - OR-95 H., Rebecca L., 1993 July 30 (2 of 3) (Box 83)
    - OR-96 H., Rebecca L., 1993 July 30 (3 of 3) (Box 83)
    - OR-97 Jane (Box 83)
    - OR-98 Jenelle (1 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-99 Jenelle (2 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-100 Jennifer, 2003 May 17 (Box 83)
    - OR-101 Jody and Lori, 1992 November 25 (Box 83)
    - OR-102 J., Janet, 2003 September 10 (1 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-103 J., Janet, 2003 September 10 (2 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-104 JSR (1 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-105 JSR (2 of 2) (Box 83)
    - OR-106 K., Daniel, 2002 November 30 (Box 83)
    - OR-107 K., Jack, 2002 November 30 (Box 83)
    - OR-108 Kamen, Paula, Jordan Rich Show (Box 83)
    - OR-109 K., Jamika (Box 83)
    - OR-110 K., Cristi, chronic daily migraine, 2003 December 7 (Box 84)
    - OR-111 Kesa, December 1 (Box 84)
    - OR-112 K., Anita (1 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-113 K., Anita (2 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-114 Labia (Box 84)
    - OR-115 L., Sarah (Box 84)
    - OR-116 Laura, 1994 February (Box 84)
    - OR-117 Leslie, Felice, Rhonda, August 5 (Box 84)
    - OR-118 Liz, Hampshire College (Box 84)
    - OR-119 Mahoney/Fersusar (Box 84)
    - OR-120 M., Arthur, Boston, December 19 (Box 84)
    - OR-121 Mary, Washington, 1994 March 29 (1 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-122 Mary, Washington, 1994 March 29 (2 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-123 Mary Elise (1 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-124 Mary Elise (2 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-125 Marla (Box 84)
    - OR-126 M., Paula, 2003 June 23 (Box 84)
    - OR-127 Michelle, November 25 (Box 84)
    - OR-128 Michigan (Box 84)
    - OR-129 Mike D., Archie, Leslie, and Mark (Box 84)
    - OR-130 Milhause (Box 84)
    - OR-131 M., Laura, 1993 October 27 (1 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-132 M., Laura, 1993 October 27 (2 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-133 M., Diana, December 28 (1 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-134 M., Diana, December 28 (2 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-135 MTV, 1993 October 10 (Box 84)
    - OR-136 Nanex (Box 84)
    - OR-137 Nevada, 1996 September 20 (Box 84)
    - OR-138 NOW (Box 84)
    - OR-139 OOB, San Francisco (Box 84)
    - OR-140 O., Arcana, September 20 (1 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-141 O., Arcana, September 20 (2 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-142 Otto (1 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-143 Otto (2 of 2) (Box 84)
    - OR-144 P&G onsite interviews (1 of 6) (Box 85)
    - OR-145 P&G onsite interviews (2 of 6) (Box 85)
    - OR-146 P&G onsite interviews (3 of 6) (Box 85)
    - OR-147 P&G onsite interviews (4 of 6) (Box 85)
    - OR-148 P&G onsite interviews (5 of 6) (Box 85)
    - OR-149 P&G onsite interviews (6 of 6) (Box 85)
    - OR-150 Palac (Box 85)
    - OR-151 P., Reverend, 1992 October 8 (Box 85)
    - OR-152 Pornography Conference, Leigh (Box 85)
    - OR-153 P., Mary, Alabama (Box 85)
    - OR-154 Procida (Box 85)
    - OR-155 R., Jeffery, 2003 June 4 (Box 85)
    - OR-156 R., Nahib, 2003 July 15 (Box 85)
    - OR-157 R., June (Box 85)
    - OR-158 Reinventing Love/Gallagher (Box 85)
    - OR-159 Remarks (Box 85)
    - OR-160 Repro Reports (1 of 2) (Box 85)
    - OR-161 Repro Reports (2 of 2) (Box 85)
    - OR-162 Rhonda/NCASA, Santa Barbara (Box 85)
    - OR-163 R., Barbara, 2003 October 29 (Box 85)
    - OR-164 S/M, 1995 March 24 (Box 85)
    - OR-165 Safe sex (Box 85)
    - OR-166 Sarah, Mark, Anderson, Karen, 1993 April 23 (Box 85)
    - OR-167 S., Lynne, 2003 November 17 (Box 85)
    - OR-168 S., Megan (1 of 2) (Box 85)
    - OR-169 S., Megan (2 of 2) (Box 85)
    - OR-170 Shedd, 1993 November 10 (1 of 2) (Box 85)